Kirito.
Yeah, Alne?
Listen, I have faith in
your skills as a swordsman,
but I have to warn you about something.
The Levantains have a saying,
handed down for generations.
Soak your sword in the
blood of the mighty,
and you will make their
strength become your own.
Like blood, blood? Yes.
Before he started here,
Volo had been engaging in first-strike
duels with real swords for a while.
As a result of that, those experiences
are what gave him his power.
His imagination, of course.
Volo's strength is tied to an
old family motto he grew up with.
So if he beats someone strong, he
believes he'll get stronger from it.
Watch out.
He aims to draw blood today so he can
wet his blade and grow even stronger.
I know you can do this.
I have the utmost faith in you.
You are not the type of swordsman
who would fall so easily to him.
Also, this is the perfect
opportunity to fulfill your promise.
What promise?
Oh, yeah, I said I'd show you
the best sword skill I had.
That's right, so show
it to me here, on him.
Done.
You'll see the best one I know.
Shall we start, trainee Kirito?
Yeah.
Elite Disciple Surlute, will you
serve as witness to this duel?
Yes, of course.
Elite Disciple Leventain
versus Primary Trainee Kirito.
The victor shall be the one
who lands the first strike.
Let it be known that both parties have
agreed to use real swords in this match.
Let's go,
let's
go.
This is the end of the
day, and it's a great day?
and it's a great day.
It's a part of the end of the day.
I hope that the power is on.
I hope that the hope is
on the end of the day.
I hope that the fire is off.
We will be fine.
I hope that the power is on the end.
It's epic!
It makes me a voice See you
livez in yourself My first
time I will see you with
eternal life I will be upon you
SHINING STORM MAN DIAMOND Happy
to be the red person Turnin
Oh my word, I didn't know painting
swords black was a custom in the boonies.
Did you, Lord Rios?
Don't be so insensitive, Umber.
It's not the poor Page's fault he's too
busy to polish the filth from his sword.
A mountain-splitting wave
of the High-Norkian style.
He's starting with his best skill.
That's Avalanche.
A heavy one-hit thrust.
But it's the hardcore version of it.
His imagination's boosting its power.
Dodging's not an option.
No.
I'm gonna have to block his strike.
I gotta promise to keep.
I have to counter with something bigger,
like the four-part vertical square.
He blocked it!
If I can hold out, I can
still get my fourth hidden!
Holy crap!
Is that the source of his power?
He's picturing his
ancestors, backing him up.
I won't lose to him.
No way.
I can't.
I'm not going to let you beat me.
Did his sword just grow?
That is enough!
Ms. Zuzurka?
If she decides the duel
is over, we must obey her.
Um, okay.
But why, though?
Years ago,
during the Four Empire
Unification Tournament,
she was the first swordsman to
represent North Norlingarth.
Trainee Kirito's punishment
is hereby fulfilled!
Next time, try not to
fling mud onto anyone.
You were lucky today.
It's back to normal.
I thought you had been slashed
Yeah, talk about close, huh?
Anyone else would have surrendered.
Oh, you hopeless fool!
That said, it was a magnificent fight.
Well done.
I am forever grateful.
On the one hand, I wish
I could have fought you?
But on the other, you did keep your promise
and showed me what you were capable of.
Nicely done.
But, um, nobody won. It was a draw.
Is achieving a draw against the first
seat not good enough for you? Uh, no.
That's not what I meant. I hope not.
The result wasn't even the point.
Seeing you fight was, actually.
It taught me something.
Something extremely important.
We can talk about it back at
my place while we celebrate.
We'll invite you, Gio,
and Lord Golgorosso, too.
Sure.
As I was watching your
match, it hit me again.
Your Aincrad style has
limitless possibilities.
As for the surlude style, I once saw it
as a practical skill, but it's too stiff.
Oh, come on.
Don't go there again.
I haven't beaten you a
single time since I got here.
Surlude style's attacks are so diverse.
In my book, that's what
makes it so amazing.
It's history as two. How?
Once, a distant ancestor of mine
angered the Emperor at the time.
And because of that,
the Sir Lute family was banished from
the official Hynorkia style indefinitely.
Oh.
So my family improvised.
And then, from that, our
non-traditional style was developed,
becoming the Sir Lute style.
I don't resent it by any means.
On the contrary, I have always
been proud of our style.
Still, I may have retained some
doubts about its legitimacy.
These two years,
I couldn't beat Volo, not because
he specialized in a better style,
but because I felt mine was lesser.
Lina...
You and I though, we both have
unique styles of swordplay.
The difference is, you don't feel inferior
to those trained in more orthodox styles.
After watching you this past year,
and seeing how you fought with
Volo in today's duel, To be honest,
I think I understand why you don't.
For me,
knowing I'm the successor to the Sir Lute's
style fills me with great pride and joy.
There is no better feeling.
Becoming your mentor is
a close second, though.
Thanks, Lina.
And now that you saw how I countered Volo,
you shouldn't have any trouble
beating him in the finals. Right.
Oh, well, well, what perfect timing.
I was hoping I'd run into
you, and here you are.
What do you guys want?
Well, naturally, I wanted to commend you
on your dazzling performance earlier.
True.
Those were some very
flashy-looking skills.
I'm certain you unnerved first-seat
Leventayne with your dashing theatrics.
Woody, you pick in a fight?
Certainly not.
A nobleman would never dare engage in
uncouth activities with a commoner.
Unless it's giving handouts.
To praise your stunt, no, to
honor your battle, here is a gift.
No need to thank me.
It is my one charitable act for the day.
Good night, Sir Kirito.
Sir nothing!
It started out as an experiment.
The Zephylia is a type of flower that doesn't
bloom anywhere in the Northern Empire.
Lena told me that they were her favorite.
it.
I tried to make them bloom,
using my imagination theory.
And along the way, I started
identifying with the flowers,
because I knew how hard it
was trying to stay alive in a
foreign place.
Having been cut off from the real
world and all the people I loved
and cared for made me feel more and
more alone as time went on here.
I shared that pain with these flowers.
I'm sorry.
Have faith.
Believe in the strength of the flowers.
You grew in this foreign soil.
Who's there?
Believe in yourself, too, for helping
them grow as well as they have.
Yeah, but it didn't matter in the end.
Worry not.
Their roots still cling
to life within the soil.
You sense it, do you not?
The sacred flowers in this garden
want to save their friends.
Their energy shall aid you.
But how?
I don't know any of the
spells that can help.
You do not need to.
The arts are only tools to
harness and refine the meaning,
or what you call the mental image.
Use your heart.
Feel the prayers of the
flowers, the ways of the world.
flowers, the meaning.
Please, help me.
I need you to share some of your power.
Imagine the flower's life force flowing
through you and into the Zephelia's roots.
Whoever you are, thanks a lot.
Ah!
Oh, my God.
Heeey!
Oh...
Match over!
Lina graduated from the North
Senator Swordcraft Academy.
She was the top-ranked student that year.
After our advancement exam,
Eugeo and me were ranked seat 5 and 6?
and got promoted to elite disciples.
Elite Disciple Eugeo, I am here to report.
The assigned cleaning has been completed.
Thanks, Tiese. Good work.
I don't have anything else
for you, so you're free to go.
Oh, and, um…
I'm sorry, Ronie.
I don't know how many times I've told him
to be back before you finish cleaning,
but he never listens.
It's fine.
I'll just wait until he comes
back so I can make my report.
You know,
if you really want,
I can always put in a good word so you can
get your mentor changed to someone else.
You're going to have a really
long year if you serve under him.
Just a warning.
Oh, I don't mind.
I knew it.
You guys were talking
about me behind my back.
Um, Elate Disciple
Kirito, here's my report.
Cleaning is complete.
Everything is shiny and
spotless. Oh, okay. Thanks.
Come on, Kirito.
These two have a lot on their
plate, so please respect that.
At least try to get back here
before they're done cleaning.
And could you tell me why you're coming
in through the window all of a sudden?
Because it's the shortest
route from East Third Street.
It's way faster than
going through the lobby.
Keep that in mind, because on days
you're running late, it's a lifesaver.
Oh, right!
Could you not teach them that?
Hang on, if you're coming from East
Third, then that bag is from...
Ha, so much for manners when your
stomach's rumbling, eh, Yu-Gi-Oh?
Here.
Here, I bought extra so you can
share some with your dorm mates.
Thank you so much, Ely Disciple Kirito!
We'll head back as fast as we can and
eat these before their life decreases.
We'll see you tomorrow!
Oh, it's full of honey pies
from the Prancing Deer Cafe.
Let's hurry before they get cold.
What's up?
Oh, nothing much, really.
It's just, I'm wondering
where your head's at.
I hope you haven't gotten
so comfortable lately that
you've forgotten why we came
here in the first place.
Like I'd forget.
We're closer now than ever.
Almost there.
I have no pain left,
and I have no pain left.
It's not your face, it's not your eyes.
If you feel like you're next to me,
I have no pain left.
I have no pain left, I have no pain left.
Next time, Noblemen's Obligations.